[
      {
        "id": 1,
        "answer": "Something in the world that you hope will change in the future.",
        "question": "Something in the world that you (wish/hope) will change in the future."
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "answer": "An activity you hope you can do when you retire.",
        "question": "An activity you (wish/hope) you can do when you retire."
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "answer": "An activity you wish you had tried on your last holiday.",
        "question": "An activity you (wish/hope) you had tried on your last holiday."
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "answer": "An activity you hope you can try on your next holiday.",
        "question": "An activity you (wish/hope) you can try on your next holiday."
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "answer": "A talent you wish you had.",
        "question": "A talent you (wish/hope) you had."
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "answer": "An activity or a course you wish you hadn’t given up.",
        "question": "An activity or a course you (wish/hope) you hadn’t given up."
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "answer": "Something you wish you had done when you were in high school.",
        "question": "Something you (wish/hope) you had done when you were in high school."
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "answer": "Something you wish had never been invented.",
        "question": "Something you (wish/hope) had never been invented."
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "answer": "Something you hope will be invented in the future.",
        "question": "Something you (wish/hope) will be invented in the future."
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "answer": "An animal you wish you weren’t scared of.",
        "question": "An animal you (wish/hope) you weren’t scared of."
      },
      {
        "id": 11,
        "answer": "Somewhere you hope you can travel in the future.",
        "question": "Somewhere you (wish/hope) you can travel in the future."
      },
      {
        "id": 12,
        "answer": "A job opportunity you wish you had taken.",
        "question": "A job opportunity you (wish/hope) you had taken."
      },
      {
        "id": 13,
        "answer": "A promotion or professional opportunity you hope you will get in the future.",
        "question": "A promotion or professional opportunity you (wish/hope) you will get in the future."
      },
      {
        "id": 14,
        "answer": "A famous person you wish you could meet.",
        "question": "A famous person you (wish/hope) you could meet."
      },
      {
        "id": 15,
        "answer": "Someone you hope you can spend time with soon.",
        "question": "Someone you (wish/hope) you can spend time with soon."
      },
      {
        "id": 16,
        "answer": "Something you wish you had more time for.",
        "question": "Something you (wish/hope) you had more time for."
      }
    ]
  